Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
Theodore Bikel papers
1946-2014
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bikel, Theodore
LSC.2321
120.8 Linear Feet (249 boxes, 56 flat boxes)
19 Audiovisual Carriers (16 unprocessed film reels, 1 unprocessed audiocassette, 1 unprocessed film, 1 unprocessed VHS)
This collection primarily consists of correspondence and subject files pertaining to Theodore Bikel's careers in music, stage, film, and television, as well as personal and family matters, and political and social activism. Also included are sheet music, scripts, and screenplays; clippings and ephemera; audiovisual material; awards; and a small amount of photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Golden Legend, Inc. on behalf of Aimee Bikel, 2016.
General
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9980992413606533
We are committed to providing ethical, inclusive, and anti-racist description of the materials we steward, and to remediating existing description of our materials that contains language that may be offensive or cause harm. We invite you to submit feedback about how our collections are described, and how they could be described more accurately, by filling out the form located on our website: Report Potentially Offensive Description in Library Special Collections.
Biographical / Historical
Actor, folk singer, and political activist Theodore Bikel was born in Vienna, Austria on May 2, 1924. In 1938, Nazi Germany invaded Austria and Bikel's family emigrated to British administered Palestine, where he lived on a kibbutz. Bikel got his start in acting at the Habimah Theater in Tel Aviv. He emigrated to Great Britain following World War II to study at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art, performing several roles on the London stage in the 1940s. Bikel made his Broadway debut in Tonight in Samarkand in 1955, making the decision soon after to emigrate to the United States. In 1959, he originated the role of Baron von Trapp in the original Broadway production of The Sound of Music, opposite Mary Martin. His best-known stage role was that of "Tevye" in the musical Fiddler on the Roof, with more than 2000 performances over several decades. Bikel's film debut was in The African Queen (1951); he also appeared in The Defiant Ones (1956), My Fair Lady (1964), and The Russians Are Coming, the Russians are Coming (1966), among others. He was cast in numerous television roles during his career in both sitcoms and dramas. His stage, film, and television roles encompassed a wide variety of nationalities.
Bikel was also a folk singer, recording 37 albums for the Elektra label, and sang in over 20 languages, including Yiddish, Hebrew, Russian, German, and Spanish. He was a founder of the Newport Folk Festival and was involved with planning as well as performing at the annual event in the 1960s and early 1970s. He was active in the New York folk scene in the 1960s, living in Greenwich Village.
Bikel's activism and involvement in politics encompassed a variety of areas. He served as Vice President and President (1973-1982) of Actors' Equity Association (AEA) and as Vice President of the Federation Internationale des Acteurs (FIA); in addition, he was President of the AFL-CIO affiliated Associated Actors and Artistes of America ("Four A's") for over 25 years. In 1977, Bikel was appointed by President Jimmy Carter to serve a five-year term on the National Council for the Arts. Outside of the arts, Bikel was active in civil rights and anti-Apartheid causes and was a delegate to the 1968 Democratic National Convention in Chicago. He campaigned for New York City mayors John V. Lindsay and Edward Koch. Bikel was a long-time supporter of Israel and was especially active in Jewish causes; he served as Vice President of the American Jewish Congress (AJC) and was also interested in the welfare of Jews in the Soviet Union.
Bikel continued to perform and be politically active until shortly before his death. He died on July 21, 2015 in Los Angeles.
Scope and Content
This collection primarily consists of correspondence and subject files pertaining to Theodore Bikel's careers in music, stage, film, and television, as well as personal and family matters, and political and social activism. Also included are sheet music, scripts, and screenplays; clippings and ephemera; audiovisual material; awards; and a small amount of photographs.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
Subseries 1.2: Loose and hanging files, 1962-2012
Subseries 1.3: Actors' Equity Association subject files, 1960-1985 Subseries 1.4: Writings, circa 1960-1993, 2000s
Series 2: Musical arrangements, 1940s-2000s
Series 3: Scripts and screenplays, 1951-2014
Series 4: Photographs, 1950s-2006
Series 5: Memorabilia, 1944-2014
Series 6: Audiovisual material, 1957-2014
Actors -- United States -- Archives; Singers -- United States -- Archives; Bikel, Theodore
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  Scope and Content
  Series primarily consists of chronological correspondence and subject files containing both professional and personal material.
  For searching purposes, please note that Bikel used the British spelling of theatre and generally referred to Fiddler on the Roof simply as Fiddler. He also used numerous acronyms in his label titles; some of the more common ones are listed below.
  ACA: American Council for the Arts
  AEA: Actors' Equity Association
  AIMA: American Israel Music Alliance
  AJC: American Jewish Congress
  EBM: Executive Business Management
  FIA: Federation Internationale des Acteurs
  JWB: Jewish Welfare Board
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    Correspondence files are usually divided into personal, business, and fan mail. Subject files pertain to Bikel's Elektra recording career, concert appearances, and the Newport Folk Festival; his acting career in general and specific stage, film, and television productions; business dealings, management, and investments; political activism and Bikel's involvement with various organizations, including the American Jewish Congress (AJC), Actors' Equity Association (AEA), National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), and others; and travel.
    This subseries also contains correspondence from or items relating to Bikel family members, especially parents Josef and Miriam Bikel; see early correspondence in boxes 1, 2, 224, and 226, as well as files within individual years, usually labeled "Bikel" or "Family". The bulk of this material is in German.
    Arrangement
    Files are mostly in the order presumably kept by Bikel: generally chronological, then filed alphabetical by title within each year, usually with uniformly printed labels. Accordion and other large subject files that encompass several years are filed at the end of the appropriate decade.
    - ABC "Flair", 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Academics, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Academy of Television Arts & Sciences, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Academy TV, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - AIMA, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AJC - Arts Chapter, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - AJC misc./personal, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress Arts Chapter/East Coast, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - AJC West Coast Arts Chapter, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - AJC misc., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - AJC Met., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AJC East arts, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AJC West arts, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Apartment 8336 DeLongpre, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Apartment, purchases, etc., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - ATVAS, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Benin Oil, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Book file, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Brecht-on-Brecht, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Caucus with Backus file, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Concert requests, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Concert requests, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Concert appearances, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Concerts, etc., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Concert notes, etc., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Conklin, Alice, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Conklin, Alice personal, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Directions '61, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - EBM, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - EBM, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Elektra, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Elektra Records notes on recordings, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Elektra Records, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Elektra forms, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Elektra, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Elektra, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Executive Business Management, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Executive Business Management, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Fan mail A - E, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 2-7)
    - Fan mail F - K, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 1-6)
    - Fan mail L - S, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1-7)
    - Fan mail S - V, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - A - K fans, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2-6)
    - L - Z fans, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
    - Misc. hate letters, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Half Moon, 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Half Moon Productions, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Half Moon, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Half Moon, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Hanson & Schwam, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hanson & Schwam, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Hurok office, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Interviews - radio & TV, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - IMF, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Jim Mahoney Associates, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - KPFA-KPFK - correspondence, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal, Harold, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Leventhal, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Lohman Oil, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hurok, Sol, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Job applications, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - MCA agents, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - McFadden, Eddy, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Meridian Books, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Meridian Books (World), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Music Corp. of America, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Music Corp. of America, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - National Jewish Hospital at Denver, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - National Jewish Hospital at Denver, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Nat'l Jewish Hospital of Denver, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nina Music, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Personal appearances, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Personal appearances, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Personal appearances: Requests, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Quartermoon, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Quarter Moon, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Radio Program: At Home with Theo Bikel, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Radio Program: At Home With Theo Bikel, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - (Theodore Bikel at Home?), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Sane (nuclear policy), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sound of Music, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    - Sound of Music, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Sound of Music Tickets, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Sound of Music, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Steiner, Ashley, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Steiner, Ashley, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Stevenson for President, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Triangle Bowling, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - WBAI, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Wolhandler, McFadden Eddy, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Publicist
    - Wohlandler, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Early correspondence (bulk family), 1946-1961 (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 1-3, Box 224, Box 226)
    - Correspondence and subject files, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence and subject files (loose), 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 5-11)
    - Correspondence A - personal, 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - T. (Bikel) personal unanswered, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Family correspondence, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bikel - personal, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bikel - business, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Mixed Correspondence, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - personal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - business, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence A - personal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence A - business, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence B - personal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence B - business, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence C - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence C - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence D - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence E - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence F - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence F - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence G - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence G - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence H - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence H - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence I - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence L - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence L - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence M - personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence M - business, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence N - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence N - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence O - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence O - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence P - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence P - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Q - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Q - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence R - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence R - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence S - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence T - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence T - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence U - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence U - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence V - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence V - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence W - personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence WX - business, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - (Loose A), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Personal corres., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence A, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence B, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
    - Correspondence C, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence E, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Family correspondence, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence G, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence H, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence I, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence J, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence K, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence L, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence M, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence N, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence O, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence P, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence R, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence S, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence T, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence W, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence XYZ, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - (Loose correspondence), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - A general, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - (Loose - bulk A), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - B general, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Mama, Papa Bikel, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bikel statem., 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bikel personal, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - (Bikel), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - D general, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - E general, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - F general, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - G general, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - H general, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - I general, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - J general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - L general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - N general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - O general, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - P general, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Q-R general, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - S general, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
    - T general, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - U-V general, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - W general, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - X-Y-Z general, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - A gen, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - B gen, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Bikel misc., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Bikel personal, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Misc bios etc, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Includes 1962 appointment book.
    - C gen, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - D gen, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - E gen, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - G gen, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - H gen, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Jac Holzman Inter office re Theo, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Hurok, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - I & J gen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Insurance, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ITA, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - K gen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - L gen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - M gen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - N gen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - NY State - Arts Council, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - P gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Q & R gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - S gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - T gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - U & V gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Tent House Theatre, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - W, X, Y & Z gen, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SNCC, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SNCC bulletins, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Mahoney publicist, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - VID (Village Independent Democrats), 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - (Newport Folk Festival), 1963 (Box 28, Folder 4-6)
    - Bible readings for album/ presentations, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Strays - '62-'63, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - (Appointment book), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Commentary (journal), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Academics, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - AEA, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - AIMA, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - AJC misc., 1964 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - AJC Arts E. Coast, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Ashley-Steiner, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - A personal, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - A general, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - B general, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Cafe Crown telegrams, opening, etc., 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights - misc., 1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Columbia Records, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - C fans, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - C personal, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - D general, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - D personal, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Equity - Canada, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - EBM, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Seamus Ennis, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - E general, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - E fans, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Films, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Folklore Productions, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - F personal, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - F general, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - F fans, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Free Southern Theatre, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - G fans, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - G general, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - H general, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - H fans, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - I & J general, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - I & J fans, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ITA, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - K fans, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - K general, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - L fans, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - L general, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Leventhal newsletters, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Leventhal, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Long distance telephone poles, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - M general, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - M fans, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - N fans, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - National Committee for the Arts in America, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - O fans, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - O general, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - P general, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Proposition 14, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - P fans, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Pelham Manor, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Q & R fans, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Q & R general, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Bette Rosen, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Scripts, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Subscriptions, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - S fans, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - S general, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
    - SINA, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Tourists International, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - T general, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - T fans, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - U & V general, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - U & V fans, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - VID (Village Independent Democrats), 1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - W, X, Y, Z fans, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - W, X, Y, Z general, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - White House, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - (Appointment book), 1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - (Appointment book), 1964 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - General, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Personal A, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Fans A, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Academy, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - AEA, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Airlines, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - AIMA, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ACRAF, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - AJC, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Ashley-Famous, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - General B, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Barclays Bank Limited, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Trade Bank & Trust Co., 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Broadside & other folk news, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - B personal, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Bikel misc, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Bikel personal, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - B fans, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Commercial Bank, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Commercial Bank of North America, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - C personal, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Civil rights, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - C fans, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - D fans, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - D general, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - D personal, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - E general, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - E fans, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - EBM, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - EBM master file, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Elektra, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - F fans, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - F general, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Festivals, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - F personal, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - G general, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - G fans, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Globe Star, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - G personal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - H personal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - H general, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)